That's your main course.
They're soft, they're moist.
They're for babies.
Finally, one more pass
with toilet paper,
maybe clear out that
excess moisture.
Maybe treat yourself
to a blow and go,
if you can get you a hair dryer.
Just about 30 seconds
would do you good.
The fuck?
Year.
What?
What year is it?
What kind of dumbass
question is that to ask?
We have 8 weeks of boot
camp ahead of us, men.
That'll get us
toned and prepared
for all manner of combat.
Not working out at all.
Masking tape.
It is no friend to
chilled aluminum.
Velcro. Color-coded, efficient,
environmentally friendly.
Who is he talking to?
And why is he dressed like
a registered sex offender?
Can we focus for a
moment, ladies?
Please, we need to talk about
next month's meal plan.
Obviously, everyone
hated the ceviche.
I read the suggestion box.
I'm gonna stop you right there.
I see through this weak act.
You may have fooled Colossus
with this nice guy shit...
but not me.
Don't be mean.
Back off, NTW.
No, no, no. Let her go.
Let her go, it's okay.
She has a right to be skeptical.
Look at me. I'm an easy target.
You know, historically,
mischief has been my mistress...
so I understand, you know.
But I like to think...
that you guys have
really rubbed off on me.
I like to think that I've
rubbed off around you, too.
A lot.
And for the first time
in a long while...
I like me.
I accept your apology.
I never apologized.
I was talking to your heart.
See? You're not lost
cause you thought.
I'm proud. You're everything
I knew you can be.
Thank you, Colossus.
Just trying to be the
world's best X-Man.
Sorry, X-Person.
Hmm. Something wrong
with the soap.
It's fine.
I just filled it. Give it
a few more pumps there.
Now, if you'll excuse me...
it's dust bunny season...
and I'm hunting wabbits.
Bye, Wade!
Fuck. Fuck you.
No one is born perfect.
But you can be.
I know you're doing
what comes naturally.
You can't help yourself.
But you can.
It takes work, discipline...
and treatment.
Your abilities...
I know how seductive they are.
How powerful they make you feel.
But you must learn
never to use them...
so they will never use you.
Please don't cry.
I'm going to help.
I'm gonna make you feel
what you should feel.
How you need to feel...
every time you're tempted
to act upon your urges.
Suck my mutant dick,
you four-eyed fuck.
Wade.
Wade!
Come in! Hey, I was just doing
a little bit of light
reading here...
We have mission.
Well, you guys be
safe out there.
I'll be praying for you.
No, I want you to join.
I'm sorry, what?
You heard me.
Trust me, that's
a terrible idea.
I'm really not ready.
You are ready. I'm not.
Be at the X-Jet in five.
I can do thirty.
Now. I can do now.
Final offer.
Irene Merryweather, WHIT News.
Live here at a breaking
news situation
at the Essex House for
Mutant Rehabilitation.
A mutant boy is
appearing to have
some sort of an incident...
with police here behind me.
RUSSELL: Get away from me!
There are two police vehicles
that are overturned.
There are open fires. Fuck off!
Stay back!
A scene of absolute chaos here.
Calm down.
I'll burn you! You stay back!
Get away from me!
You wanna fucking die?
And it appears as if the
X-Men are arriving...
Scatter!
With what appears
to be a trainee.
Everyone, calm down! The
pros are here. I...
We're the X-Men!
A dated metaphor for
racism in the '60s.
So, respect.
At ease, Officer.
What are you doing?
My job!
You're the one who
said I was ready,
and I frankly
disagreed with you.
But here we are, trying to
overcome our differences.
Like Beyonce says, "Please..."
"Please, stop cheating on me."
Hey!
This is the fifth incident.
This kid needs to be in
the Ice Box, not here.
Russell belongs in our care.
Not in prison. I assure you...
we have everything
under control.
Stay back! I'll burn you!
Not getting a real
"under control"
vibe here, Marty.
It is Glen, isn't it? Daniel.
I'll ask the questions, Miguel.
Let me talk to the kid.
You stay here with your
weird, secret sex lips.
You wanna die?
This kid's adorable.
I don't know why I packed
the hollow points.
I'll burn your balls off!
First day. I'm so nervous!
Did you just say
"hollow points"?
Yeah, probably should've
brought a Super Soaker.
Hi, there!
Stay back or Justin Bieber dies!
Justin Bieber. He called
you Justin Bieber.
Hold on! Wait, wait, wait!
Okay, let's not do
whatever that is.
Okay? Let's just talk!
It's Russell, right?
Firefist.Firefist.
Ooh, that's a great name.
Where does it burn?
Just the fist, or all the
way up to the elbow?
Definitely all the
way up to the elbow.
Come quietly, or there
will be trouble.
You stole that from Robocop!
That's from Robocop!
Just stand down!
You're embarrassing me.
Look, Fire...
Oh, my God! I can't say it!
I'm so sorry!
Oh, shit! That fucking does it!
Put your hands behind your knees
and get down on your head! Now!
Wade! What was first rule?
Label everything in
the refrigerator!
Do not escalate! Rules
are meant to be broken!
That's the exact opposite
of what they're meant for!
Fuck! Fine!
I'll start from the beginning.
My name is Deadpool,
and I'm an X-Man.
Trainee! Shut it!
Look, I get it.
All right, you're scared.
Alone.
You got no family.
I didn't have a family, either.
You live in this dump.
Guess what?
I used to live in a
shithole just like it.
But you know something?
A wise woman once said to me...
"Speak up."
"I can't hear you with that
pity dick in your mouth."
Too much? I went too far.
That was effervescent.
Stay in school, kid.
Or don't. I didn't.
And I'm an X-Man.
Trainee.
Fuck it!
Superhero landing coming up!
Ah, fuck, fuck, fuck!
That is so not practical.
I could get used to
this X-Man shit.
Trainee!
Get a power restraint on him.
Now!
Calm down, squirt. It's over.
We got ya.
What's that do?
Power-dampening collar.
Shuts down all mutant abilities.
You can't get it off. Unless
you've got a grenade.
Huh. Could've used one of
those in the first act.
Thank you!
That was absolutely thrilling.
True heroism in action.
We are in your debt.
We can take it from here.
Take me to the Ice Box, please!
Anywhere's better than here.
Believe me, son,
you do not wanna
go to the Ice Box.
That place makes Hitler's
anus look like Waikiki.
Let's get you inside, young man.
No, wait, wait. Wait.
You guys stay there.
Those guys hurt you?
Who?
Baldilocks? Jared Kushner?
Both of 'em?
Oh, fuck it.
Four or five moments!
I'm sorry?
That's all it takes
to be a hero.
People think you
wake up a hero...
brush your teeth a hero...
ejaculate into a soap
dispenser a hero.
But, no, being a hero
takes only a few moments!
A few moments...
doing the ugly stuff
no one else will do.
No!
Stand down! Hold your fire!
Wade, what did you do?
Colossus, no!
You were right, Wade. You
are not X-Men material.
No shit, Shiny Gandhi!
What was your first clue?
The hollow point through
that fuckhead's face?
That kid was abused!
You can always tell!
COLOSSUS: We have rules!
You are not judge,
jury or executioner!
Fuck your rules! I fight
for what's right!
And sometimes you
gotta fight dirty!
You let me down for
the last time, Wade.
Okay, get these guys in the pod.
Take them to the Ice Box.
Hey, baby!
I wonder what gang I'll be in.
Yeah!
- Is there, like, a Sorting Hat?
- Hi.
I've always seen myself as